Mufeed Dawood

Lynnwood, WA +1(425)426-6913 I mufeedashraf@yahoo.com

Objectives

To participate at the Leap program at Microsoft that will enable me to use my strong background experiences and knowledge, and award winning experience, and ability to work well with people in the tech field, as I have a great and friendly interpersonal skills and an ability to perform multitasking duties in a fast-paced environment, and willing to learn and grow in the tech field.

Experience:

Automotive Technician at Precision Tune Auto Care

SEPT 2016 - Present

- Repair and replace defective equipment parts, using hand tools and power tools, and reassemble equipment.
- Test components and systems, using equipment such as infrared engine analyzers, compression gauges, electrical readings, and computerized diagnostics devices.
- Inspect drives, motors, transmissions, belts, and filter, or perform other maintenance actions to meet manufacturer's performance specification.

Crew Member at McDonald's

March 2017- March 2018

- Maintain high standards of customer service during high-volume, very fast paced environment.
- Communicate clearly and positively with other coworkers and management.
- Took initiative to find extra tasks when schedule duties were completed.

Volunteer Work at Maintenance and Church Department November 2011- June 2013 (2 years) Coptic Church, School, and Hospital at Lusaka, Zambia

- Perform installation and maintenance of desktop/laptop computer systems and associated software and peripheral devices.
- Organize and maintain the cleanness of the church, and help in Sunday school session.
- Helped in moving and fixing hospital equipment.

Education:

Lynnwood High School

2015-July 2019

Member of National Honor Society for Recognition of Scholarship, GPA: 3.9

Edmonds Community College

Mechanical Engineer

SEPT 2017-Present

Edmonds Community College Honor Roll, Fall Quarter 2017-18, Winter Quarter 2017-18 GPA: 3.8

Skills:

Interpersonal communication

Leadership

Analytical

Proficient working on hands on projects

Trilingual

Computer and internet skills

References are available on request.